[Music]
Brother, this is what I need.  Drive him away right now.
So this is that insect catcher.  And can it really
catch insects?  Come let's
test it.  So sometimes you see
such small insects come into our room.
Then the insects arrive.  And now
if I have to chase it away, it will
not run away.  He will have to be killed and
killing doesn't feel good, friend.  So now let's try
holding it with this.  So look here, we have to
put this on top of this [music].  And
look here, there is a big magnifying
glass installed with the help of which I am able to
see it in a much bigger size.  And
from here it has to be closed like this.  And this
is our insect closed.  And look
friend, this insect is trapped inside it.
And now let's leave it outside.  So now let's
leave it here like this.  And
look, it's gone.
So yes, according to me, this is a
very good thing.  It is worth the money in my
opinion.